<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bi0sctf2024 on Azr43lkn1ght</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/bi0sctf2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bi0sctf2024 on Azr43lkn1ght</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 01:15:43 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/bi0sctf2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Batman Investigation III - Th3 Sw0rd 0f Azr43l bi0sCTF 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20III%20-%20Th3%20Sw0rd%200f%20Azr43l/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:43:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20III%20-%20Th3%20Sw0rd%200f%20Azr43l/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Points: 1000&#xA;No. of solves: 1&#xA;Challenge Author: Azr43lKn1ght&#xD;Challenge Description:Azrael the Archangel of Vengeance has joined the batfamily after destroying the machine of St Dumas defeating face to face against his most startling foe, the undying heirophant, the first son of St Dumas. The Dumas is not completely destroyed and the heirarchy out somewhere out, Jean Paul, our Azrael has a shared workspace with Duke Thomas, The signal. St Dumas got them now by sending the weapon of azrael but we got the attack process captured by signal as he was the one who let it in unknowingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batman Investigation II - Gotham Underground Corruption bi0sCTF 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20II%20-%20Gotham%20Underground%20Corruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:43:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20II%20-%20Gotham%20Underground%20Corruption/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Points: 1000&#xA;No. of solves: 0&#xA;Challenge Author: Azr43lKn1ght&#xD;Challenge DescriptionAfter getting in hold of Carmine Falcone&amp;rsquo;s Laptop, Bruce Wayne has to investigate his laptop but unfortnatly he can&amp;rsquo;t get the files nor the encrypted disk and its key, so he went ahead to get the memory dumped. After investigating and getting the data from the guy hired by Falcone for analysis, it seems corrupted!. Now He have to find and solve the things uncovering the Gotham&amp;rsquo;s underground secrets, Help him solve the case of biggest Gotham corruption that is yet to happen!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
