<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Threat Hunting on Azr43lkn1ght</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/threat-hunting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Threat Hunting on Azr43lkn1ght</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:18:53 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/threat-hunting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Batman Investigation IV - The Last J0ke bi0sCTF 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20IV%20-%20The%20Last%20J0ke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:26:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20IV%20-%20The%20Last%20J0ke/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Points: 1000&#xA;No. of solves: 0&#xA;Challenge Authors:&#xA;Azr43lKn1ght&#xD;,&#xA;Jl_24&#xD;,&#xA;sp3p3x&#xD;,&#xA;gh0stkn1ght&#xD;Challenge Description:Bruce Wayne was alerted that Joker have escaped from Arkham Asylum, Joker with all the Gotham outlaws crafts a letter for Bruce, He wants to make it go all crazy x_0!,and now Batman gets a message sent to Him with a letter, but apparently as Damain was in the Desktop, he opens it and everything goes crazy, the letter is now distributed to everyone in gotham, if Batman doesn&amp;rsquo;t find a fix, There is no stopping the chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batman Investigation III - Th3 Sw0rd 0f Azr43l bi0sCTF 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20III%20-%20Th3%20Sw0rd%200f%20Azr43l/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:43:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20III%20-%20Th3%20Sw0rd%200f%20Azr43l/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Points: 1000&#xA;No. of solves: 1&#xA;Challenge Author: Azr43lKn1ght&#xD;Challenge Description:Azrael the Archangel of Vengeance has joined the batfamily after destroying the machine of St Dumas defeating face to face against his most startling foe, the undying heirophant, the first son of St Dumas. The Dumas is not completely destroyed and the heirarchy out somewhere out, Jean Paul, our Azrael has a shared workspace with Duke Thomas, The signal. St Dumas got them now by sending the weapon of azrael but we got the attack process captured by signal as he was the one who let it in unknowingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batman Investigation I - Like Father Like Son bi0sCTF 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20I%20-%20Like%20Father%20Like%20Son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:43:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Batman%20Investigation%20I%20-%20Like%20Father%20Like%20Son/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Points: 998&#xA;No. of solves: 3&#xA;Challenge Author: Azr43lKn1ght&#xD;Challenge DescriptionDamian Wayne stored a secret in his old pc, but Dr. Simon Hurt who got this information, planned a contingency against Damian by the help of Starlab&amp;rsquo;s techies, poor Damaian was so eager to view the encrypted secret file that Raven sent him long back but Simon knows this piece of information as well as the decryption process, will he win this situation like a Wayne?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
