<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DFIR on Azr43lkn1ght</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dfir/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DFIR on Azr43lkn1ght</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 02:01:09 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dfir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Malware Development, Analysis and DFIR Series - Part II</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Malware%20Development,%20Analysis%20and%20DFIR%20Series%20-%20Part%20II/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 02:01:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Malware%20Development,%20Analysis%20and%20DFIR%20Series%20-%20Part%20II/</guid>
      <description>Malware Development, Analysis and DFIR SeriesPART IIIntroductionIn this blog, we will cover the important topics in x86 assembly.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s not really a languauge, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have higher level of abstraction or almost no abstraction at all, it&amp;rsquo;s basically machine code that is in human readable form, gives more direct control over the processor, but it indeed requires more writing due to very less abstraction and it&amp;rsquo;s not easily portable.&#xA;There are only 3 possible datatypes in the processor level, depending on the number of bytes the processor accesses: Byte(8 bits), Word(16 bits) and Double Word(32 bits).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware Development, Analysis and DFIR Series - Part I</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Malware%20Development,%20Analysis%20and%20DFIR%20Series%20-%20Part%20I/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:43:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Malware%20Development,%20Analysis%20and%20DFIR%20Series%20-%20Part%20I/</guid>
      <description>Malware Development, Analysis and DFIR SeriesPART IIntroductionThis will be a series focussed on developing Malwares for ethical purposes only, The author is not liable for any damages caused.&#xA;before we begin, let&amp;rsquo;s know about a few things&#xA;what is a malware?Malwares are malicious softwares, that are a nefarious class of software meticulously engineered to compromise the integrity, confidentiality, or availability of computer systems. These pernicious programs are often cloaked in deceit, masquerading as legitimate software to trick unsuspecting users into granting them access.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
